https://www.flagshipbank.com/Other/flagship_privacy_policy

WFBC Shareholders
PersonalChecking/Money MarketSavingsCertificates of Deposit/IRAsPersonal LoansMortgagesNew Mobile BankingSecurLockMy Money ProgramBusinessChecking/Money MarketSavingsCertificates of Deposit/IRAsBusiness LoansOther ProductsE-DepositACH OriginationOnlinePersonal Online BankingBusiness Online Banking
Menu
PersonalCheck/Money MarketSavingsCertificates of Deposit/IRAsPersonal LoansMortgagesBusinessCheck/Money MarketSavingsCertificates of Deposit/IRAsBusiness LoansOther ProductsACH OriginationOnlinePersonal Online BankingBusiness Online BankingAbout usContact
Flagship Privacy Policy
WHAT DOES FLAGSHIP BANK DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal
law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand
what we do.
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
• Social Security number and Income
• Account Balance and Payment History
• Transaction History and Account Transactions
When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons
financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons Flagship Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit
this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does Flagship Bank share your information? Can you limit this sharing?
1. For our everyday business purposes— such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal
investigations, or report to credit bureaus:
Yes, Flagship Bank shares
No, you cannot limit this sharing
2. For our marketing purposes— to offer our products and services to you:
Yes, Flagship Bank shares
No, you cannot limit this sharing
3. For joint marketing with other financial companies—to offer our products and services to you:
Yes, Flagship Bank shares
No, you cannot limit this sharing
4. For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes— information about your transactions and experiences:
No, Flagship Bank does NOT share
5. For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes— information about your creditworthiness
No, Flagship Bank does NOT share
6. For non-affiliates to market to you
No, Flagship Bank does NOT share
Q. How does Flagship Bank protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures
include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
Q. How does Flagship Bank collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
• Open an account or deposit money
• Seek advice about investments or apply for a loan
• Tell us about your investment or retirement portfolio
We also collect your personal information from others such as credit bureaus or other companies.
Q. Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only:
• Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthiness
• Affiliates from using your information to market to you
• Sharing for non-affiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates – Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies–Flagship
Bank has no affiliates.
Nonaffiliates – Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies–Flagship
Bank does not share with non-affiliates so they can market to you.
Joint marketing – A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or
services to you–Our joint marketing partners include Card Assets, LLC & EconoCheck.
Do you have Questions? Contact Us
© Copyright 2020. All Rights Reserved. SitemapBack to top
Checking / Money MarketPersonal SavingsCertificates of Deposit / IRA'sPersonal LoansMortgagesBusiness BankingBusiness Savings
Certificates of DepositBusiness LoansSwitch to FlagshipAbout UsBusiness Online BankingPersonal Online BankingOther Products & Services
Terms of UseSecurity StatementCalculatorsID TheftPrivacy PolicyLost or Stolen Cards
0
